okay well I was I was supposed to I
guess bring my camera on when I came
back here but I forgot so I'm gonna have
to use the cell phone which was Brawley
not a very good quality but anyway so I
haven't been here for a couple of weeks
now so I guess I'll check out the
results of my experiment with liquid
papers and God knows what else was in
there it does appear to have frozen kind
of no smells really bad yeah this
kinda looks like scientific discovery
no there's a geological activity in
there I mean no traces of blackness must
be a Mel Gibson fan whoa here it's
interesting here we have little rocky
thingies there kinda looks like salt I
don't think I put anything like that
there hmm weird and here wait a minute
it's kind of a mixture between God knows
watch God knows water and God knows what
he's sort of like greyish and hmm what
I'm gonna do I guess it was just put it
in storage and
wait until I can think of something else
to do because there's not much stuff in
here unless you want to play video games
or something
Mario's time machine or our Sim City
pretty fun game in a while filming I
think I must have trade off my mistake
it's time I clean up here because I got
things there that drive stuff in there
mostly things nobody cares about
keep purge that's it's the I guess
localization well some guys would
transform or something this is some
arcade stuff space area that's pretty
good Heroes of Might and Magic tape
recorders iPod the way they used to to
be I guess I don't know how you open
that anymore
put it deep in there and yeah so anyway
I I'm kind of a loss to what to make
here I could make a ginger ale and rice
krispie squares cocktails or something
anyway I'll complete this video when I
have an idea which might be in a long
time who knows
November 23rd Wednesday and the first
day of snow
legend
have the best restaurant in Montreal go
there and it's just outside
remember this place
I was
sambuca pilgrimage long time ago I've
claimed to scratch there and yeah so
about people following me they're
running really fast I think they've got
weapons or something wait a minute
okay now it's just some old lady with
her dog
that's a couple of old
italian-looking weirdos talking on their
cell phones I forget it no matter what
is
sambucas there so we're safe
sambuca
it will make it all go away and there's
a little guy over there and lucky can't
see him because he's pretty far away in
the picture but he's splitting in a
little Christmas sign he's hidden by the
tree so he can't see him but I can he's
quitting the little Christmas sign there
that was there last time I came with the
video but that wasn't there until
yesterday little Christmas thing you
there
so yeah
I think I have an idea of what I'm gonna
cook it off gonna have to eat something
alright see you guys I found my new
passion in life fun bubbles wait a
minute oops
okay I'm up it's safety but it was on
the ground I don't want to get STDs let
me think it's not working okay ah how
does this work how the kids do all these
balloons I made a few I could be doing
this like all day yay my god I love this
so much
okay I'm gonna actually try to cook
something something healthy this time
something that's eatable want some water
and put it on the boil machine I'm gonna
make some vegetable stuff so have these
Greenpeace and these lentils so you get
the proteins and also I think I have
some vegetable here and maybe olives
that's really vegetable but something
for the taste this stuff
hmmm vegetable juice maybe and for the
taste I guess
okay maybe some mustard and honey that's
probably it I guess mmm some of this
stuff okay I think I have four it's not
be expected ingredients I thought I had
more stuff but it's like improv you know
when you're cooking you don't really
know what it's gonna be
okay so let's wait until this thing
starts to boil
okay the water's boiling and as it was
heating I left my camera here and it was
too close to the thingy so there's like
I think the screen started to milk a
little bit or something
anyways so sorry okay so we're gonna
start with the ingredients and the thing
about the kitchen and cooking is that
the order in which you add the
ingredients doesn't really matter
because the only important thing really
is what you've got in there because it's
the nutritious value you know like if
you read on the back of the box it says
like you know like how much thingies you
have on this thing so it just adds up
with the other ingredients it doesn't
like anyway mustard for the taste
oops
it's like beachy
I hope it doesn't stick to the button
okay some honey for the sugar and the
face it gives a little bit of calories
too so it's good
calories are good gives you energy okay
and an apple cider vinegar it's like a
vinegar it's like an acid so if you've
got bad stuff and your buddy it just
melts it away you know I feel like an
optimist or something okay
yeah I'm gonna add starts
I don't know why cooking me some reason
there's just something kind of sexual
about it you know can't look it yeah
yeah okay and this one that you guys
know I'm very pessimistic about this
recipe because you guys can't tell from
your computer screen but I can tell from
here because I'm here in person and the
smell coming from this isn't good so
that's what always a bad sign when
you're cooking in a doesn't smell good
but you know bad signs aren't generally
you know it's not automatically means
that it's bad you know it's like you
know if like you're a dick turn screen
or something and you think you have an
STD and you go to a doctor you don't you
it's nothing so it's the same thing with
picking and it smells bad and you think
maybe it's gonna taste bad but then it
actually tastes good even if it smells
that so it's okay wonder what happens if
you had kosher and halal ingredients in
the same recipe that's probably gonna
explode or something there's a little
thinking inside them so wait
I think it's gonna melt
yeah smells so bad whoo ah that's weird
that need to put some perp you are gonna
take out the wooden stick later yeah I
think it's ah yeah I think it's rotten
yeah good the case then we're gonna put
in the a boom and um this stuff it's
like killer what is this some Arab
pistachio thingy or something
ah pissed ocular this thing's pretty
good yeah I hope they don't stop put me
on the terror watch because I eat the
Arab Kennedys but you never know these
days and the world we live in the way
until the Apple gets absorbed yeah it's
time to take out the obstacle and I
think that that smell I was feeling was
it wasn't the recipe was the rockton
thing whole pension stuff whatever you
call it
okay no I'm gonna have to cool it off
cause it's
so I can't actually taste it until
there's a temperature change
put some ice I think one day I'm gonna
make a recipe that works so well I'm
gonna become a billionaire father of
bodybuilders in the world are gonna be
buying my recipes that you know
supplements shops instead of buying
whatever had the hell it is and they
they buy their okay um how am I gonna
taste okay I'm a little bit scared yeah
let me giving it yeah okay
oh man that tastes like rotten vegetable
juice if I leave this on the counter for
a few months and then I drink it it
tastes like that oh boy
ah okay well whatever I know it
sucks but at least you know I had to
cook something it has been so long but
yeah don't get killed guys and yeah so
that's how it is and if you guys are
still alive make another cooking thingy
eventually and in the meantime I'll just
go sleep or something
so a house I forgot to put it in
the teller I would have been a nice
addition to this recipe no maybe next
time then bye bye guys