I'm in the car wash got the get anti
rust treatment today so when I wash the
car like before I go in I missed those
places that have like these kind of
weird orange thingies that kind of like
turn around like like big brushes or
something like this place it just it
just like blows like some kind of water
or something the cleaning in theory or -
at some point
[Music]
Hey look my teaching mr. happy
well I was kind of cute or something I
guess
yeah so my remote starter doesn't work
either for some reason like this thingy
that I had installed like it used to
work but now it doesn't and at some
point like I had to change the car
battery and as soon as I change the
battery the remote starter stopped
working I think it got like deprogrammed
or something and I googled like how to
program it and this way too complicated
I might see dump you in case the cops
come in here
[Music]
we
and that sign over there
I don't think anyone here is gonna try
to drink the water up to think of a
session and open the windows it's just
yeah I'm up we'll open the windows and
look there's sirens outside like these
flashing lights like they well it's not
the cuffs cuz the cops is blue and red
it's like yellow flashing lights usually
that's for construction vehicles or
something I think it should be almost
over now
[Music]
let's go to the drying thingy
on board I wonder what happens if you
start the wipers while you're doing the
dry and the drying thingy they like fly
off or something I shouldn't be driving
while holding the the camera but this
one could the parking lot over there I
don't think I'm gonna kill anybody
hopefully
it's 7:33 so pointment is a cleat in the
morning anyway there's some guy over
there so I'm gonna do a summer down
we're gonna get super mad that I'm
filming him and he's probably gonna
think I'm a Soviet spy or something
anyway so uh yeah whatever let's go get
this thing Richard I guess no it's early
but I guess I'm just gonna go see you
guys
[Music]
might not be able to do anything about
the starter since they're not the ones
who installed it but whatever they said
they're gonna look at it anyway I'm
walking in the cold it's too early I
think the Sun bucha shops closed can't
go buy any that's too bad the delivery
only wonder what happens to go in there
and they get arrested or something
that's this guy doing over there
that's delivery only dude yeah well
whatever just gonna get out of here
before he gets arrested
someone knocked down the no truck
parking sign
as you get a fine then you get told that
you if you park your truck there or
something if you're not a authorized
vehicle whatever
they know this grocery store it's called
the maxi there was a murder in there a
couple of years ago in 2016
she look it up the Montreal grocery
murder it's it's right in in here and it
was a pretty bad thing I mean I went
back I guess a few days later and all
the employees looked pretty gloomy
to say the least was a really sad story
and this dude he was he had a crush on a
girl and obviously the girl we didn't
give a about him so the guy can
catch a clue so instead of you know just
looking for other fish in the sea gets
obsessed with her and he just you know
came here one last time and well asked
her out she said no again and only
barely stabbed her which is
completely ridiculous it's just like
seriously but whatever that's horrible
anyway
they wondering why they put the pumpkins
outside the store you know what if I
still want nobody's gonna see me and
come on you're supposed to like take one
and then like go inside with it and
that's weird
[Music]
oh well
so many airplanes here
all day long one airplane after the
other it's been like that since they
moved the airport back to go to the city
he used to be outside it's cold
[Music]
and they had to translate stop signs
into French I guess that's because
people who don't speak English didn't
know that meant to stop so they just
kept going crashed into people or
something I mean I would be the only
logical reason to spend that much money
anyway that's I think it's closed it's
too early
because nobody no cars in there
[Music]
well just come back later
and another airplane
yeah
out
[Music]
onion ring chips yeah like the the
ketchup chips was at the best they try
different flavors I've seen
pizza-flavored chips from Lay's but it's
a limited edition so I don't know how
long they're gonna sell them for and
obviously it's a disgusting idea but
maybe I should try them at least at
least once until they before they did
they stop they stopped making them
Mazda car shucks
anyway it's called hands are freezing
anyway see guys some other time
be brave