this is little thingy there the white
strip because when I mean I didn't know
like how to push this house together
correctly so it was like see like this
here's a hand like black like empty
spaces between the tiles so I filled it
up with my wait a minute
with one of these touch with this thing
either see so that's the floors
[Music]
kind of yeah yeah I bought this pizza
okay that was hungry and it says wait a
minute oh yeah the preheat the oven to
is a 485 degrees in my camera nice
glasses I think so yeah and the problem
is that hey this is the oven it's kind
of like proceeding but it's just
smelling really really bad
it's easy oh god this they're still
because what happens that I use this
soapy thingy they're like this thing and
it's just that I think I put too much
and it's smelling really like soap
in it I think I need some water or
something
they let me use this thing Oh
because I put a lot of soap to clean up
with like aluminum thing but the problem
is that the way I remove all the soap
but it was hard
is the problem if I put the pizza in all
this soaps smoke is going to rise up
okay let's just let this water evaporate
there for a sec and I'll wait a minute
it's going to be awaited because if this
thing is hot yeah there has to be a way
to remove the soap because I have to get
it wet to wipe it off but I don't
know and that thing is
wait a minute I think something's broken
oh what the hell's going on here
how do you remove the soul I mean it
just flew to the bottom like that
anymore
damn it I don't want to eat the soapy
pizza it's just going to kill me it says
if I would just drink that thingy right
like that I don't know I have to
think of something later
ouch there's going to be some kind of
way I think ah well let's just let's
just leave it on boiling paper if I can
attach toilet paper to this thing wait a
minute I'll have much time saver left a
point of it let me if I can wipe it
that's the only long thing I have if I
can just put some point P from the tip
there
and you can play I got a bad feeling
about this
wait a minute yeah maybe what the toilet
paper would suppose don't get a catch
fire what things don't get charm
usually that's women ouch feel like
I'm drinking the swamp here wait a
minute ouch ah not easy
ah god damn it's now it's breaking apart
let me just remove I'm Jojo okay
something's not working okay
now let's think about this logically
there has to be some kind of a solution
there has to be something that can
oh I don't know anyway
I'm immortal anyway I mean I haven't
died yet have I please I don't think so
yeah so I guess I'll just leave it like
that then