oh friend just give me this new coffee
machine let's try this see if I can set
up apparently it's really good
let's see how it works now
so this is an instruction manual I don't
know why it would be an Italian but
whatever okay
yes well that's how much a mission like
this is tough
probably this one you don't put powder
in it you put bucks like these little
things just 200 cups and comes
oh that's amazing I have to go back home
to get the converter plug where the hell
that guys in Montreal get a coffeemaker
with a European plug oh well I guess
I'll get back to this video once I go
back at home for my plugs all right so I
guess see you guys later
well I was for all sorts of troubles
this last video for example I got this
converter but it's broken see there's a
little thingy there in it and besides
what I also learned this because this
thing yeah okay so 120 volts that's good
but it's a thousand watts and because
it's a cakewalk I wouldn't have been
able to use something like this in the
first place
apparently I would need a bigger machine
to be able to use it so let's see
I guess it's too small
yeah I was able to push it in had to be
like really strong and I guess that's
okay okay let's see
you can't things off okay they have to
put water
Oh LS this thing there so I have to put
water in there okay okay let's go
I suppose that's prolly enough water
okay and then put the coffee capsule and
then put the cup
okay let's see okay take this off I'm
going to use one of the clubs
if I take this off I can close it
yeah like this maybe that's how it's
supposed to be okay I was able to close
it and it making one noise
put this here and look I'm supposed to
push the button when I wanted to make
the call
supposed to take that water
Ernest
there's smoke coming out of it
I guess it's working Oh after all this
hard work I thought I get to try the
coffee me from this machine
unfortunately I can't put this cup
underneath there because it's too small
so I have to use one of those cups as
before and then let's see mm yeah this
okay it's just normal coffee I guess