you know so I'm gonna be making one of
my favorite tasty drinks
it's called sunrise because it kind of
looks like a sunrise so we're gonna take
like some Kennedy syrup looks like blood
or something and orange juice so it's
pretty simple thing it's a little bit
strong okay ah I'm putting a little bit
of a bottom of the cumin ah smells good
this is disgusting by itself but it can
be good when you mix it with something
when I put a little bit more this up put
a little bit more of the orange juice
then the tequila so it goes up a little
bit higher that's heavy
okay
okay I was about here okay it's a little
bit more like look I think that's all
right and there you go
see it looks like sunrise with red and
and orange
great tasty stuff
so I think I'm gonna go to sleep it's
thanks pretty good with sleeping pills
that makes you have like a really funny
dreams you know it's like I'm probably
gonna be dreaming that I drank blood or
something is read like that yeah good
night guys