well so I'm kind of lost here not really
sure which way to go and I'm hungry I
need pizza wait okay so here's can go
straight left or right I think I've been
here before I'm going around in circles
okay this is Carrie look I'll get back
to you guys when I'm home so we can eat
some pizza okay
I'll see you guys later I'm hearing
screams now
I know if you guys can hear them it
looks like someone's being tortured
oh god oh god okay I think I better go
the other way I have no idea where I am
this way that way oh okay let's try
this way
feel like I'm in Skyrim or something
Oh getting a bit tired now what I found
hmm yeah I think I need sambuca
seriously and pizza and sambuca and a
lot of coffee ideally this strange shoe
print sale with two little circles like
that looks like some kind of alien
footprint Oh mod of the force now hope
there was no sauce collection there this
is a baseball field over there you got a
feel were a bunch of elderly black
people go to cultivate plantains or
something well I'm not too far now god
I'm thirsty and hungry
I wonder what the hell that stuff is huh
anyway I made it over there that's the
sambuca shop I know why I'm getting lost
in the forest to buy some book I want to
have a car but anyway so
alright we're there alright I'm back
let's see hmmm hard to open
oh yeah okay
damn I'm hungry
that was long walk oh there was no
Sasquatch or anything okay
oh all right feels good mmm okay so I
make pizza I need something to put it in
high okay
I use one of these director make pizzas
around but when you I have so I'm gonna
do some floor we're gonna mix the like
to put them like we need to make how
that's not a spoon we need to make like
a paste or something you know
so normally got a mixed floor with like
water
sambuca or whatever yeah
oh okay let's see let's try to make
something works okay I'm gonna make
Gordon Ramsay crowd okay kinda hug do
one hand all right
smells good
well thanks good big good pizza gee is
there like some kind of guy to tell you
how much water or something or whatever
compared to flora that has to be because
I'm kind of like just guessing not do
feet might as well use them okay holding
like masturbation practice or something
take your hand stronger okay
it's starting to look like based or
something okay okay that's good maybe
where's the spoon spoon spoon spoon okay
that's Pune spoon oh yeah it was right
there ah let's see
has to be big enough at least look like
a pizza you know okay and I think they
kind of I think when I see people mix
for with water but like eggs do so we're
the second oh all right some eggs okay
all right thanks kind of liquidy as well
so it's sort of adds to the sort of
thing there needs more water I gotta
save something drink as well we have one
cup okay wait a minute
any types of strategy to kind of hold
this together there okay and cooking
your stuff you always have to remember
all their thingies and I'll and stuff
you know I wonder how many chefs are I
think put some booth on their pizza cuz
it will leave you to stand up and use
the sensor to get some water I mean you
never know what restaurants they don't
actually show you the grates them you
know this is great they just bring you
the stuff to your plate you know so
don't eat pizza and drive they don't you
never know what they put in there
okay
oh just kind of starting to look like
pizza okay all right so yeah I gotta use
a olive oil because I don't want it to
like stick or something you know because
if you don't put oil if you put this
thing in the oven it's gonna like stick
you know so yeah I was doing pizza
pockets the other day it was all like
sticky and disgusting stuff okay I'm
speaking about gotta preheat this thing
let's see that's 450 Celsius or
Fahrenheit er whatever um okay
dammit okay uh-huh
so that's that part of it okay so we're
gonna put the pizza ah disgusting my
hands are all honey okay ah goddamnit
yeah it's all sticky it's not supposed
to hear you wash in the movies when they
make pizza the cab like throw it in the
air and all that you know it's all round
and beautiful looking and and then you
know put it down okay
god damn it
it's complicated I who the hell invented
cooking why do you have to make it so
complicated
I'll have a word that that guy okay it's
not gonna be like perfectly 100% round
but at least it's going to look round
enough when it's baked we can like maybe
cut away a little bit at the edges so
that it's rounder but at least uh okay
it's kind of looking like a pizza I
suppose I mean it's round enough we just
need to put the actual pizza stuff over
it
okay okay
kind of looks pizza is enough mm yeah oh
god my fingers are disgusting wait a
second uh just what uh oh yeah yeah yeah
look yeah you know they never show you
in those cooking shows like when you
fingers get all sticky and everything
you know it's like propaganda by Gordon
Ramsay because he doesn't want you to
know how difficult cooking actually is
okay now pizza you need tomato sauce
make some where's the other tomatoes I
bought like a bunch of em don't know
where I put them oh well then I'll find
them eventually look at this so
yeah okay okay so that's the blender
working okay back off with my fingers in
their song youtube someone actually put
his fingers in the blender bloody mess
you know when it turns you can actually
press on the thing in the middle to stop
it with your fingers you know and the
guy try to do that at will actually end
up losing a couple fingers okay why is
it the menos always make me think of
Italian ladies
okay seriously
goddamnit there's something they don't
show you the movie seriously there's
always like a part missing where's the
baby oh stop it
okay
stead betting on okay so my mom
seriously is at that part
dammit
seriously yeah if I crush them or
something's gonna be better wonder how
they do it on TV when they have like 10
seconds like to cook up all wrong
why does it look like milk seriously
doing a milkshake I'm doing pizza feels
kind of violent
okay whatever I'm doing is not working
okay let's just I don't know what's
going on here but ah me that blender was
like a couple hundred dollars supposed
to be able to blend tomatoes of all
things seriously god damn it that's all
the white stuff seriously
alright I guess I got to do it myself
yeah
okay all right I'm gonna remove some of
that crap in there okay well baby this
can blend
let's try seriously god damn it don't
damn it
okay they say alcohol solves all the
problems seriously
Oh
okay now did I use the slow thing key it
looks like a mini prison oh yeah damn it
Oh where's it uh yeah okay okay so the
liquid stuff's supposed to go down what
stays here is kinda like the tomato
sauce so to solid to be tomato sauce uh
Running Room just whatever you think
okay so a good pizza supposed to have
some tomato sauce in the middle this
looks more like octopus sauce for some
reason okay
well you can't say it isn't real
Tomatoes not like chemical think he's
put in and tell you it's Tomatoes you
know what I give you the pure okay
okay see looking like a pizza and pink
and everything
the geese may enjoy it as well okay
where's the cheese okay oh yeah I'm
going to put some cheese how do I open
this
oh okay god damnit whether there's so
many obstacles that you know ah
seriously after Taylor now I know what
Jaime Lannister feels like when he's
cooking no okay
see doesn't that start looking like a
pizza and is looking like a piece of to
me right now
yep yep yep this is gone good good pizza
okay and I have the salami pepperoni
finger whatever about the difference
okay
mmm smells like pizza now making like so
design or something well fortunately I
don't have mushrooms but it's been
really nice okay so that's that part of
it
no oh yeah ah these thingies how long is
this video gonna be okay okay okay
okay that's kind of looking pizza ish
something something related to pizzas
like uh humans are to monkeys or
something uh okay it's really hot in
there alright almost as hot as it was
outside to date okey there were pizzas
in the oven so let's uh
come back in whoa ten twenty minutes or
something and we'll see what it looks
like that yay Oh little by little huh
it's kind of boiling at the bottom there
I hope it doesn't stick I mean we did
oiled the thing you didn't we oh well
swell a little more it looks like a
pizza but it doesn't smell like a pizza
anyway we'll see well it hasn't been
very long but it sort of kind of looks
ready doesn't it oh wait a minute
let me just aah oof it's hot Hey
okay yeah kind of hmm kind of okay let's
just turn this thing off okay and we're
gonna use these thingies right strategy
okay
ah
with okay
hmm don't know if it's ready though but
interesting a knife
wait hey it isn't sticking okay got a
thick though wait a minute how am I
gonna hmm
okay from here to here
shit's gonna break one two three oh wow
halfway there
no not on the floor okay I'll give this
one to my mother-in-law oh oh god
do her this
close enough
yeah okay
still kind of win the mill let's try to
pace that stuff hard to cut okay let's
see weights so oh wait it's too hot
like it's still a bit hot I'm gonna just
let it cool off a couple mist and try to
taste it hey it's been a few minutes so
kind of hot but not burning anymore
those kind of look Oh wet here no let me
try
mmm
it's
actually good it's just that I mean when
you first bite into it it tastes like a
normal pizza
it's just that you know once you
actually start chewing you know and
you're starting to swallow it
then it's starting and then it gets
really sweet it's like it's the sambuca
you know sambucas really sweet but when
you bite into it it tastes like salty
like a pizza then you know you keep
chewing and it ended and it starts
tasting super super sweet all of a
sudden it's kind of strange it don't
taste it right away mmm
well I guess that's um hmm well it's
okay I mean yeah well next time I'm not
using some bucha I mean it's good but
could be better and why so yeah that's
it
I guess my god gotta finish this now
yeah
oh I saw see you guys some other time