oh hey guys laughs you were a hundred
years old you're gonna recognize this
thing a boy Bob I got three games on it
Tetris Robocop do I hate to walk up to
the game's impossible and hit how it's
in view from school color each time he
was a final process of that lunch
ah don't listen I'll be 32 stuff
supposed to be able to turn you to like
a bunch of stuff or something
this is like I know soon wanna appétit
like winning
[Music]
machine not a ninja lose this one a trip
just be like the secret place this used
to be that secret chapter and like the
first game sometime you'd like your
lender like you know when you're on the
pitch at some point to just like
randomly like to end up at the bottom of
the pit and fight him he's like yeah
yeah Blue's gonna kill you flying around
[Music]
no no whatever gives us a way we're
gonna be making some well need mushrooms
these thingies that's some celery this
time it's good they just put this stuff
there so I think oh hey Todd they make
this finally got this faucet fixed then
broken for like a thousand years
[Music]
I'm gonna cut all this dick a million
years
[Music]
hook it to the power just just put that
in the blender
[Music]
there's no room anymore it's kind of
like fill to the top there you know it's
gonna
[Music]
Oh
when I wasn't know like I should be a
blender with like lathes on like ever
just put it like that in the thing just
that's water so that boys
okay all right yeah I want to put some
Salvage like have a nice touch
[Music]
they're just working or what that one
this broke and I'll put that on this one
the hard way you have to look at the
little drawing this one is left like
this one I think that the big one is
broken well I mean first sometimes but
not always know why I think there's like
some kind of wire in the middle that
broken or something all right
that mushroom and celery and yes after
week boiling or something all right
okay it smells bad so it means it's it's
working yeah so now we wait until it
boils
mmm I'm gonna play some more
Mortal Kombat or something that you're
like that's just wait
starting to smoke guess it's a good
thing or something supposed to get like
softer okay I think it's working
sort of
harshly I hate this thing
[Music]
[Applause]
something that's with Gordon Ramsay oh
he says alright my god smelling like
mushrooms cause something's I'm doing it
right oh yeah and then all right no
you're supposed to put like cream or
something make it thick I wanted to come
up this side no okay to like cut them
with that brother like boiling a nice
time today
like Dean just wanted to infuse a little
bit you know what's branches like stayin
there and they're not like edible they
met towards the time branches others you
Oh burning up
exposed to be mixed like really quickly
sometimes where else just gonna fly off
there's something about smoking spot oh
no no don't come off the side
ouch ouch just like burning let me just
turn this thing off put in the blender
maybe don't get stuck at the bottom okay
all right hey where's the cover oh okay
mushroom soup here I come
[Music]
I'm supposed to put like milky stuff
slow
some cheese
all right smoking that smells kind of
weird even one end hold it there okay
just a little bit it looks creamy enough
I think that's good
[Music]
okay try this out here like anything in
the CIA smelling or something okay let's
try this out
tastes kind of bland actually hmm yeah
me yeah it's okay
mmm yes it doesn't doesn't taste much at
all anything it can barely taste a
mushroom I mean it smells like a
mushroom soup but it tastes it tastes
like water you know it there's like very
little taste to it must've we had
probably put enough stuff or whatever
huh make it better want something anyway
so um I guess it's okay I suppose
I'll see you guys some other time okay
all right