okay so yes we're gonna be pretty much
done here a little chicken okay it
smells disgusting
yeah us no yeah no all the way here
I love it
ah oh I'm gonna forget about it
yeah yeah I'm gonna feel sick man that
smell was so oh oh okay you know
what this we're gonna have this
orange juice or something yeah that's
gonna be it but I think rotten chicken
might be a good hundred easyacc or
something so I want to you know have my
sister over I'll give her some of that
work you know so I haven't given up or
something yeah
okay let's I'm gonna make two cups of
deep
stephanie's things with my fish long
time realizing that so yeah thanks like
a jacket a box of something this is
old-school cooking and a lot of people
generally talk about old school they
mean like the sixties or seventies when
I talk about old school I mean you know
biblical times back when you had you
know all these guys from the Bible like
you know Judas and Moses and whatever
else you know and they're like prancing
realm feels and picking things up
everywhere I'm out there
this is turning brown that looks like
yourself let's wipe out their plate you
know I've been thinking I made a lot of
videos about philosophy and all that I
realized people generally have a hard
time making the distinction between a
premise and a conclusion you know it's
it's amazing how little people
understand about the true nature of
things people get cut off in language
and social customs and norms and you
can't forget where things came from then
again that's why I need to start my own
religion well you know have cooking
orgies and anyway so let's come back
once this D is all properly infused and
everything will see all this goes say hi
well I think Artie is pretty much ready
we're gonna try out with a cup or
something you know I think historically
for every successful attempt at eating
something you know there's been like
chameleon unsuccessful like cheese you
know I mean you know cheese essentially
you know rotten animal titty milk you
know so I guess she had bunch of guys
for like doing orgies or something and
they got that you know animal fitting
milk and they were kinda like rubbing it
over themselves something and you know
they started thinking yeah it tastes
good when we drink it then I know at
some point some some kind site to like
keep something about or something and
they couldn't drink all of it it turned
to cheese and well yeah that that's good
you know but that's a stroke of luck
because you know it worked but it
doesn't always work always have people
who died sacrifice themselves or
something okay let's see this is this is
D whoops none of the stuff is supposed
to follow this it's not supposed to be
mixed with infused by it right that's
the purpose of peas and future okay this
is kind of high-tech but whatever you
know cannabis smells like spinach or
something okay um I want to add this up
fifty lictors make it more tasty like
that let's see now that's got like some
sort of chocolate
I'll call drinker okay my fingers aren't
strong enough
oh wait a minute
okay well have some pretty small fingers
I mean you know check my muscles you
know finger biceps there but so so this
is the little kind of D vegetable or
thingy there
smells good it actually does
okay let's see
well um what does it taste like
yeah that's we're gonna make sing from
something good eventually this scan like
that ever part of the trial never thingy
there I don't know it's like mm-hmm
scan of fights that it's disgusting but
it's kind of addictive uh not forget it
okay I just feel kind of weird now
little bit drunk or something
ah this list is gonna smell
like really really bad tomorrow morning
okay I gotta go to sleep or something
now