okay it's been a while since I made any
new videos there's one thing that I was
kind of wondering it's about how to make
oil specifically peanut oil and here's
the thing if you think peanuts
yeah the mystery is this yeah okay open
this up
how do you go from this did this all
liquidy and I mean it just doesn't say
here any oil will burn if overheated the
I figure that up hard way yeah so it
doesn't say anything
not Canada does taste like peanuts
that's well it that's what it is like
liquid peanuts
since they're both peanuts I guess maybe
if I put it here I can do some kind of
mechanical element experiment thing
might make the peanut merge with the
other stuff that's former peanuts you
know that was transformed into some kind
of a liquidy stuff substance thing yeah
I don't get it I mean I can get you know
all those because you just crushed them
and yeah it's kind of squishy and
everything so it's no wonder would be
made into uh into peanuts liquid thing
there
this shouldn't make these holes easier
to put things and the objective of a
poll is to put stuff and you know
I don't see it's kind of getting shiny
you can see the little you know on the
peanut the little thingies that kind of
shine there whatever storage dolmens
close well
so lots are exactly what's happening way
the transformations probably occurs you
know where you where you got that the my
poems so I'll try to push the peanut you
know to the place where there's a little
bulbs there that are going off where
there's one on the other side there it
is it's going to keep it in the bolts
because that's the hottest area
I think wind chill transformation
well me the only way you can make
something liquid is heat right I mean
think something solid and it's like you
know the low atoms that are rounded like
that are making it
they're turning and the faster they turn
that the more the softer they get you
know so like if they get like really
really fast it turns liquid and then
gets faster faster it becomes gas so I
suppose that's what they did they kind
of yeah they heated the peanuts to make
them liquid but then the problem is that
they stayed leak with even at normal
temperature after that so they probably
added some something like they might
have eaten or something I don't know not
to make it set its face liquid whoa whoa
oh whoa oh I hate that
Oh
oh yeah
Wow holy wait a minute
well this only happened to me I wonder
how many people died making this stuff
that officious dangerous yow
oh okay so yeah that was a failure
yeah that's the thing with oil it's just
blows up in your face when you try to
get it like in Iraq you know on paper so
yeah I'm not made out to be a cook but
um I guess it's kind of like trial and
error you know I got a you got to suffer
to learn stuff so something like that I
guess anyway so I'm gonna go back to
sleep or something ah good night or
something