[Music]
you do some yard work remove some weeds
paper bags supposed to put the weed in
that thing there's so much
like the bonus like all the good plants
they just died because this random stuff
starts growing you know and when you
pull it out you have to remove the roots
as well or else they just they just grow
back put some random stuff here it's
really full of stray cats
[Music]
technically plants are alive right like
hey it feels like when I'm removing
leaves I'm actually committing genocide
or something
well I'm not the only one
[Music]
that's what's this data weed or just
some random thingy that just whatever
like a tree or something no branches no
leave yeah well don't know the stands
are alive this thing
that's um poison ivy yesterday there's
almost tempted to try and make deal with
it but I decided against it
and this one's bad
that goes like thingies they look like
flowers but they're not flower just
means I just leave their pigeons singing
or something yeah yeah disgusting just
dead for centuries
[Music]
ah no this was supposed to be beautiful
with all like different kinds of plants
and each square and everything I only
have big projects and like he it's gonna
be beautiful I'm gonna plant a lot of
and then like five years later you
wake up is like oh wait a minute
like just weeds going in there all these
paper like oh man rains like the bag is
ruined I keep the bag inside until the
day were like the city people come in
and and collect them
ya know why I'm doing this now September
to almost winter should have done this
earlier in the year so that's a plan
that should be maybe one day we'll be
able to garden all year long but
apparently you know global warming
doesn't actually warm the planet you
know they call it global warming but
makes the planet colder is like when the
polar ice caps milk you know it creates
cold water you know because you have
that one when the ice melts you know the
water that it turns into is so cold you
know so you have a bunch of cold water
coming you know down in the Atlantic
that's a lot of heat and the cold water
makes the climate colder so it was
global warming but you know it has a
sort of strange cooling side effects
might be winter all summer something I
don't know some are all winter and
winter all summer maybe just do a little
switcheroo or something anyway whatever
let's just
higher higher just like a small
percentage of what they sell actually
Canyon tires in English mystery is full
of mushrooms you got like the leaves
that fall like years and years
cannulated dead leaves or something
hiding here
oh boy my god
just pull it right out think like on my
errand
[Music]
okay wonder if your noble looks like
this now playing soccer
oh gee dad I think we're gonna get
through it all right
I think I'm gonna go back and I need to
drink