yeah so it's kind of difficult to eat
something when you got no idea this one
is there's still some in it but I know
if I want to drink it oh it would have
been okay stop you when you don't know
like the stuff it's still good at the
stuff that expired a thousand years ago
[Applause]
okay I make some bread weird stuff in
there this nail thingy it's think it's
from there's no date on it but I
remember it was here someone left that
here like in 2001 or something like that
maybe even before that so it's just I
put tape on it yeah whatever just some
what kind of thing sometimes just put in
the freezer and leave it there just
funnel water okay let's make some toast
but I don't have like a toaster
after thingy there but I I don't know it
should all be the same kind of thing
because you know like and you're
toasting bread like this heat that makes
the other thing like black okay now we
can do is turn the Sun and you prepare
the bread I think that with food is dead
some food is salty some food is sugary
so like you can't really mix this if you
want to have a sugary toast you could
put something like that right I have
here Trident and sky like dummies gums
are we're going to have some of this the
Arab thingy there this is no bombs in it
okay but I need something to hold it
just so that
mmm yeah I was probably kinda like a
fish hook to lower it and bring it back
up but wait you know there was stalking
this guy some thinking my mind is this
depressed you know cuz he had a break
and everything trying to tell him it's
always a silver lining to everything
just like they think of something really
sad say like there's the famous you know
female celebrity who dies or something
you know I mean you're all depressed no
but you go look at like the positive for
example like once she's dead you know if
she has a the autopsy or something like
you can read the autopsy in here now
then it's gonna tell you like you know
if she shaved her foots a year she had
like a landing strip whatever so like
you're going to know stuff about her
that you wouldn't have known unless she
was a porn star or something but she was
just a regular actress so I mean you
know you can always make best out of
point um I want something that's going
to lower the bread on the okay
whoa whoa whoa that's too much
okay there you go
remove this one though
kind of a temporary okay here with the
dose is done for you turn it off okay I
can start seasoning you need to plate or
something
okay this one busted dirty clean it
sometimes uses a towel now this one's
kind of yellowish because I like my dick
every time I pee so this one is I don't
know if I can use that that's my gas
mask
this one's more clean okay
I think I'm gonna go to sleep soon
anyway I don't know what time is strong
like or something almost are good at
guessing the time okay so now you know
the thing about bread is that it's kind
of like full of little holy whole like
whole that aren't really hold that they
can like go halfway through now so when
you have things like that that melt on
it it's kind of like it gets absorbed
you know and you can like well it like
if you have for example like coconut
butter or something and you're like let
it melt inside it it's going to kind of
like get up sort and go like in the
middle then you put it in the fridge and
it solidify so it's going to solidify
inside it's like completely absorbed or
something I'll put some of these
thingies there well that's easier
because you can crush it like that I
suppose not okay that's enough
yeah the cops come here they see all
this bother we're going to think I'm
sniffing coke something smelled bad I
think yeah I want these like few months
ago and I just kind of forget about them
okay yeah this gift smell coming from
somewhere whoo
what's the smell oh where it's coming
from
scrappy something smells bad but haven't
cleaned up here inside a while
so you know what I have in here is this
vampire dollar oh yeah a little horse
that's this that was long time ago these
little things just pop up randomly
kitchen in pictures cell phone all this
can Egan $12 these are maybe once I
think these are euros shouldn't forgot
Ivan I don't know they were there
oh what's that I haven't said that
cards probably expired 10 years ago or
something anyway okay so I'm going to
have to apply heat somewhere to have
this thingy wait I'm going to try again
with this but I'm not
hmm if I can have heat here but wait so
I could have something that would
because I want the stuff in there in the
middle to melt so that in kind of like
liquid fire or something and and
oops I think lights went off does this
work do you mean if I put them in there
wait I don't know it's complicated
wait technically it should now
okay I'll know what happened I think the
camera just shut itself off for some
reason
oh yeah it's working it is getting kind
of liquidy gain will be easier to toast
maybe add some water
[Music]
whoa
um
okay the crisis is fully gone or
something
it's like these fat girl - just hang
onto your you tell him you don't wanna
okay
all this rich very stylish
suppose it should be all that bad
let's see now you can get something here
it smells pretty good though that's not
something ok ok ok be gleaming see
oh yeah it's kind of ready sort of out
oh that's still too hot
oh okay let's try I'm kind of scared
tasting it give me give me
yeah no the little thingies are
falling it's kinda like people jumping
for a while she said or something okay
hmm have to lure myself I don't
like opening my mouth now my knee is
like I'm giving a blowjob or something
okay let's see yeah I don't know
where they spit it there's Rock
disgusting stuff mmm just touching it
mmm
it's missing something long whatever