hello welcome to the desert like
everything is completely slowed down
right now
look there's a car there all right
that's fun it's like playing fallout or
like The Walking Dead you can kind of
see the ruins of civilization
oh there's a person there I got to stay
away also we're gonna catch a virus or
something we'll just go this way
that's another car there like that
street over there used to be like always
traffic jams and anyway yes
morning rush-hour is easier now but of
course there's no reason for there to be
a rush-hour because there's nobody no
one that's going anywhere so there's no
rush to go anywhere anyway this little
supposed to be there are some people
there try to zoom on them with are they
somewhere over there yeah they're seated
in the mill they're had a meter away
from each other
maybe I don't know okay
I'm hungry I need some food
and I went to the grocery and yesterday
and I was wearing my gloves
just kind of got a cold and so when I
walk in like everybody has to be in line
to wash their hands right so there's
like the lady before me with a kid and
like they're taking a long time and
washing hands and soap and everything
then it's my turn and I just I just
start washing my gloves I forgot to
remove them I ended up having wet gloves
and then I think about it and the guys
behind me are kind of getting innovation
because they want their turn to wash
their hands and anyway so I did my
groceries with wet gloves that's okay
ah another person yeah.well
think we're far away from night it's
funny cuz like oh there's more cars now
wonder where they're going is everybody
going grocery shopping or something I
gotta go buy toilet paper
hmm I mean we aren't in complete
lockdown yet so we're still allowed to
go outside without getting arrested oh
there's a video of some guy in Italy
apparently just walking around outside
is like five cops taking him down I mean
technically the cops are outside too
soon they arrest each other I don't know
made to have an exception or something
but people are so jogging I guess
they're so like a semblance of normality
well let's go this way
it's funny how people are like always
afraid of others these days like you
you're walking around someone is like
walking the opposite direction on the
sidewalk and like you guys at someone
you're gonna cross each other you know
and they're sort of like looking at you
like you know like you're some kind of
polar bear or something because you
might carry the virus I wonder what
these metal things I'm gonna call here
but these metal thing is rounded yes
like they put all these rocks like to
make some kind of like artistic barrier
or something but it's like there's metal
thingies around them it's been like that
for years wonder if like they're gonna
put some kind of liquid in there you
know to like have the rock sort of merge
with each other and then remove the
metal cage or something or if it's all
just gonna be like like this forever
with like the mental it looks kind of
weird like a cage or something
he looks like there's plastic cans or
something the Heineken but lie oh it's
beer cans but light and soft beer that's
like a crush something like an orange
crush or something that's ice-t I think
wonder if I'm doing some kind of
trademark infringement by filming this a
Pepsi I co thought of that like this
that makes this place look like garbage
like rocks there
that's kind of funny and there's nobody
what if someone comes in to water a
trees or something Coors Light like
tough for a beer or something
there was a car over here probably was
thinking it oh yeah they just hide the
rest as rocks but they just put like I
[Music]
heard that Kentucky
some people they got pissed off because
the government is saying you know don't
have groups of people together so they
decide to show it up to the government
and they held a corner virus party and
then turns on one of them actually has
the virus now so if they want to get the
virus to prove a point or something
kinda weird though I mean as soon as you
I mean you reading the papers is like a
hundred people a lot of a million who
have it then you just throw a party with
your buddies and then you have it do it
sort of makes it seem like maybe more
people have it than they're saying
yeah because from the numbers it looks
like the odds was like you know catching
the lottery or winning the lottery or
something but anyway cameras stopped I
wonder if I'm that much disk space left
I think that's what it says anyway
there's a McDonald's further down that
road I don't know if I want to go though
I don't think like the restaurants open
but like you can't eat inside you have
to like go with your car or something
this is someone who stink too close to
his dogs gonna affect the poor puppy
yeah well let me just go it that way
I can't you know seem to shake the
feeling that with this virus thing is
like if the entire planet has social
anxiety now or something
[Music]
see
we're supposed to be building more
sections of the park here but that
cannot continue the construction this
whole thing is new wasn't there before
[Music]
these things are I started them they're
planting stuff hmm it's like some kind
of industry there huh I guess I'm just
gonna go get some sambuca or something
and then just go drink sambuca I suppose
that's what you usually do it it's up so
have fun guys and stay far away from
everybody and I'll see you some other
time I like