okay well I have a little mouse problem
we can hear them the ceiling well let's
see if I can drop weight but this is the
mouse poison thingy so wait wait let me
just put my gloves on just in case
something terrible going on there oh
wait a minute okay hey and flashlights
okay let's put this thing oh I'm really
afraid now okay wait
let me just get some poisoned there
okay I don't want like a mouse to come
jumping at me as soon as I opened this
okay make a camera shot itself down for
some reason
okay let's see
that's a scary stuff are they mice do we
see them alright let's just write oh
should I be worse I guess
all right let's so let's wait until
tonight to see if there's so much noise
in the ceiling I mean I think what
happens is that if one of them eats it I
mean the others are gonna uh well we'll
see hopefully there's gonna be no more
mice or rats or whatever squirrels or
whatever it is that's up there yeah so
that's that okay so see you guys later